[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅみ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "趣味"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'げんきん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "現金"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'にっき' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "日記"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'あつめます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "集めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "弾きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'あらいます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "洗います"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うたいます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "歌います"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かえます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "換えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うんてんします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "運転します"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'よそくします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "予測します"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんがくします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "見学します"
    }
]